[
  {
    "question": "1 + 2 =",
    "top": "1",
    "bottom": "2",
    "left": "3",
    "right": "4",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 3 =",
    "top": "1",
    "bottom": "2",
    "left": "5",
    "right": "4",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 + 12 =",
    "top": "11",
    "bottom": "22",
    "left": "23",
    "right": "24",
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 12 =",
    "top": "11",
    "bottom": "12",
    "left": "13",
    "right": "14",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 2 =",
    "top": "1",
    "bottom": "2",
    "left": "3",
    "right": "4",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {
    "question": " 2 + 2 = ",
    "right": 3,
    "left": 4,
    "top": 5,
    "bottom": 2,
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 4 = ",
    "right": 3,
    "left": 6,
    "top": 7,
    "bottom": 1,
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 6 = ",
    "right": 1,
    "left": 4,
    "top": 7,
    "bottom": 9,
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 3 = ",
    "right": 5,
    "left": 4,
    "top": 6,
    "bottom": 3,
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 4 = ",
    "right": "1",
    "left": "4",
    "top": "5",
    "bottom": "3",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 2 = ",
    "right": "8",
    "left": "6",
    "top": "7",
    "bottom": "4",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 5 = ",
    "right": "8",
    "left": "6",
    "top": "7",
    "bottom": "4",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 + 4 = ",
    "right": "9",
    "left": "10",
    "top": "12",
    "bottom": "8",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 5 = ",
    "right": "8",
    "left": "9",
    "top": "4",
    "bottom": "11",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 3 = ",
    "right": "8",
    "left": "9",
    "top": "13",
    "bottom": "11",
    "answer": "11"
  }
]
